<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
  <row>
    <Color>Blue</Color>
    <Rule>Rule #01</Rule>
    <Title>Take it slow. Observe risk management</Title>
    <Text>You have plenty of time to achieve your target and move to the next phase. Take it slow, observe good risk management techniques. Most traders who pass the evaluation quickly fail on their live account. Be one of the few and not the many. Follow your plan and if you aren’t quite at the target at the end of the 30-day period, get in touch, maybe you qualify for an extension or retake!</Text>
    <Read More></Read More>
  </row>
  <row>
    <Color>Green</Color>
    <Rule>Rule #02</Rule>
    <Title>The Models, Evaluation and establishment phase and targets.</Title>
    <Text>We currently only offer a standard evaluation model. Due to poor success we have removed our aggressive model.

There are two phases you must pass in order to become a funded trader.

First the evaluation Phase (Phase I) The evaluation phase is to test your trading skills and give us an idea of what type of trader you are. During the evaluation phase you must achieve a profit target of 8% within 30 calendar days with no other rule breaches. The establishment Phase (Phase II) The establishment phase is just to confirm the results of the evaluation phase. During the establishment phase you must achieve a profit target of 5% within 60 calendar days with no other rule breaches We do NOT have any negative day rules in our programs. A trader can choose when they start the evaluation process. The calendar day countdown starts from the time you take your first trade.
</Text>
    <Read More>Test</Read More>
  </row>
  <row>
    <Color>Red</Color>
    <Rule>Rule #03</Rule>
    <Title>Trading Behavior</Title>
    <Text>Its imperative that you have a trading plan, trading strategy and risk management profile to successfully complete the evaluation.

At My Forex Funds we encourage good trading behavior but do not limit a traders ability to trade in their own style or time.

We ALLOW news trading, scalping, long term trading, short term trading etc. on all accounts.
We do not have a lot size restriction for total open lots on a single account however advise all users to be wary of their risk management profile.</Text>
    <Read More>Trading activities that are used to take advantage of the inefficiencies of Metatrader. Gap trading, latency arbitrage, Long short arbitrage, Reverse arbitrage, opposite account trading are all unacceptable trading methods with MyForexFunds. Anyone part-taking in such activities will have their trades adjusted to the executed fill price that we have received from the liquidity pool. Repeat offences will result in account termination.</Read More>
  </row>
  <row>
    <Color></Color>
    <Rule>Rule #04</Rule>
    <Title></Title>
    <Text></Text>
    <Read More></Read More>
  </row>
  <row>
    <Color></Color>
    <Rule>Rule #05</Rule>
    <Title></Title>
    <Text></Text>
    <Read More></Read More>
  </row>
  <row>
    <Color></Color>
    <Rule>Rule #06</Rule>
    <Title></Title>
    <Text></Text>
    <Read More></Read More>
  </row>
  <row>
    <Color></Color>
    <Rule>Rule #07</Rule>
    <Title></Title>
    <Text></Text>
    <Read More></Read More>
  </row>
  <row>
    <Color></Color>
    <Rule>Rule #08</Rule>
    <Title></Title>
    <Text></Text>
    <Read More></Read More>
  </row>
  <row>
    <Color></Color>
    <Rule>Rule #09</Rule>
    <Title></Title>
    <Text></Text>
    <Read More></Read More>
  </row>
  <row>
    <Color></Color>
    <Rule>Rule #10</Rule>
    <Title></Title>
    <Text></Text>
    <Read More></Read More>
  </row>
  <row>
    <Color></Color>
    <Rule>Rule #11</Rule>
    <Title></Title>
    <Text></Text>
    <Read More></Read More>
  </row>
  <row>
    <Color></Color>
    <Rule>Rule #12</Rule>
    <Title></Title>
    <Text></Text>
    <Read More></Read More>
  </row>
  <row>
    <Color></Color>
    <Rule>Rule #13</Rule>
    <Title></Title>
    <Text></Text>
    <Read More></Read More>
  </row>
  <row>
    <Color></Color>
    <Rule>Rule #14</Rule>
    <Title></Title>
    <Text></Text>
    <Read More></Read More>
  </row>
  <row>
    <Color></Color>
    <Rule>Rule #15</Rule>
    <Title></Title>
    <Text></Text>
    <Read More></Read More>
  </row>
  <row>
    <Color></Color>
    <Rule>Rule #16</Rule>
    <Title></Title>
    <Text></Text>
    <Read More></Read More>
  </row>
  <row>
    <Color></Color>
    <Rule>Rule #17</Rule>
    <Title></Title>
    <Text></Text>
    <Read More></Read More>
  </row>
</root>
